Previously on The Big Bang Theory:
We now pronounce you
husband and wife.
- I love this part!
- Me too!
I have strongly mixed feelings.
So Howard's really in space?
(Scene:)The International Space Station,
250 miles that way. Heh.
(Raj:)Right now Howard
is staring down at our planet...
(Raj:)...like a tiny Jewish Greek god.
(Raj:)Zeus-owitz.
(Sheldon:)I must admit,
I can't help but feel a twinge of envy.
(Sheldon:)He can look out the window...
(Sheldon:)...and see the majesty of the universe
unfolding before his eyes.
(Sheldon:)His dim, uncomprehending eyes.
(Sheldon:)It's like a cat in an airport carrying case.
(Leonard:)You know,
it's not exactly glamorous up there.
The water the astronauts drink
is made from each other's recycled urine.